triptrivia.com 2019-03-31

# Trip Trivia

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

When registering on our site, we collect your email address and IP address.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, enter a sweepstakes, or open a support ticket.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you by gaining feedback or responding to requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send emails with trivia questions or other products and services.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you. Our partners may place or recognize a cookie on your computer, device, or directly in our emails/communications, and we may share personal information with them if you have submitted such information to us, such as your name, postal address, or email address. Our partners may link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. For example, our partners may deliver an ad to you in your web browser based on a purchase you made in a physical retail store, or they may send a personalized marketing email to you based on the fact that you visited a particular website. To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt out, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

## How do we protect your information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

## Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. This helps us understand and save users’ preferences for future visits. It also allows us to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information such as site behavior on our behalf.

We honor Do Not Track signals and don’t plant cookies or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make our site experience more efficient may not function properly.

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless an action is performed in partnership with other companies (such as entering a sweepstakes). This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website or via email. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our brand and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Ad Integrations

We use Google AdSense Advertising, Taboola, Liveintent, PowerInbox, and other ad networks on our website and within our emails. All third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads on our site. This enables them to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
  * You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.
  * You can change your personal information by emailing us.

## COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

## GDPR

GDPR was implemented in the European Union in order to better protect user’s privacy and ensure that company’s use of data is both tangible and legitimate. Trip Trivia upholds this law by not sharing your data with unauthorized parties (such as credit agencies), and not requiring you to provide personal information to us.

Trip Trivia allows subscribers to unsubscribe at any time and be removed from our database. If you decide that you would like to stop receiving emails, simply click the Unsubscribe button on the bottom of the email and we will not contact you again.

## Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices, we will notify you via email within 7 business days should a data breach occur.

## CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send trivia questions, information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market with relevant deals and offers.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Trip Trivia  
4 Mills Rd Suite 49  
Newcastle, ME 04553
